

Phone 317-910-5607

Email drew@drewgoff.com

Portfolio

https://drewgoff.com

Address

1184 Bridgeport Drive Westfield, IN 46074

EDUCATION

Indiana University

B.S. General Studies

Minors Psychology & Media Production

Recording Workshop

Cert Sound Engineering

Expertise

Technical Skills

Languages

- + HTML
- + CSS
- + SVG
- + JavaScript/ES6

Frameworks | Libraries

- + Angular
- + React
- + TypeScript
- + Sass

Design

- + Sketch
- + Zeplin
- + InVision
- + Axure
- + Adobe Photoshop
- + Adobe Illustrator
- + Cinema 4D

ABOUT

I currently work at Capital One as a UX/UI Developer. At Capital One, I work with designers and bring their designs to life by coding them in HTML, CSS (Sass) and Angular. My average day is spent coding, coming up with solutions to design problems and communicating with designers.

Previously I worked at Caterpillar inc, where I worked on a international team of designers and developers. They brought us all together to build the fourth generation operating system's user interface. We designed all of our work there in Illustrator and coded them as Web Components.

Before working at these two companies, I started my career a decade ago as a UX/UI Designer and worked my way into being a UX/UI Developer.

EXPERIENCE

Capital One

(Aug 2020 - Present)

UX/UI Developer (Contractor)

- + Work with designers and bring their designs to life in code. Code their designs in Angular, TypeScript, SVG, HTML and CSS (Sass).
- + Design interface components in Sketch and code them as components.
- + Part of a large development team that creates internal software applications for Capital One.

Caterpillar Inc.

(Sep 2019 - May 2020)

UX/UI Developer (Contractor)

- + Brought on to design and build the 4th generation OS user interface for the Earth moving division. We designed the interfaces and coded them as web components (JavaScript, Shadow DOM, HTML, CSS, SVG) to support nine software teams around the world.
- + Created Axure Pattern libraries for our design system.
- + Wrote scripts, designed storyboards, did voiceover and created 2D/3D animations; in teaching the high level management about the cost benefits of creating a Design System for Caterpillar vehicles.

Drew Goff ux/ui developer

Phone 317-910-5607

Email drew@drewgoff.com

Portfolio
https://drewgoff.com

1184 Bridgeport Drive Westfield, IN 46074

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

Deaconess Children's Hospital

Worked on a team of designers, creating the designs for the new children's hospital. My primary role was as the photographer on the team. The large scale photography work is showcased throughout the hospital.

REFERENCES

Tom Beccuee Manager at Caterpillar 309-202-7455

Sarah Schonert Team Lead at Caterpillar 309-645-3619

Ryan Stephens Technology Manager at Kroger Technology 270-832-5443

Tara Blessinger Deaconess Designer 812-431-6199

Laura Brown Marketing Manager 812-604-5649

EXPERIENCE, CONTINUED

SIGMA Equipment

(Sep 2016 - Feb 2019)

Address

UX/UI Designer

- + Work on a team of six developers as the sole UX Designer/Developer.
- + Designed software interfaces using Adobe Illustrator & Photoshop.
- + Coded the interfaces in HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, React, JSX, Babel, NPM and Visual Studio Code.
- + Meet with business analysts and project managers to design projects to business requirement standards.

OneMain Financial

(Dec 2014 - Sep 2016)

UX/UI Designer

- + Developer and designer of the framework "OneMain Elements". What makes Elements unique is it's build using Object Oriented SASS (CSS) and vanilla Javascript. What really makes it different though is that every object has been designed for exact measurements in Adobe Illustrator. This allows us to expedite UI development by reusing code and to create consistency among designs.
- + UX Designer/Developer for OneMain Financial & Springleaf Financial's phone and tablet applications.
- + UX Designer/Developer for OneMain Financial & Springleaf Financial's infonet and internal web applications.

CNO Financial Group

(Dec 2014 - Sep 2016)

Web Designer

Truth@Work

(Jun 2012 - Jun 2014)

Director of Web and Multimedia Development

INDYCAR Driver Simona De Silvestro

(Jun 2012 - Jun 2014)

UX Designer, UI Developer and Photographer